Jason Grohoske 1520 25th Street, Apt 301 Everett, WA 98201 (419) 889-7963

Friday, January 14, 2022

To Whom It May Concern,

I am interested in the Z Networks' Graphic Design position. Most recently I worked at PSG Washington Inc. in Everett, Washington as an Account Manager. Before this position, I spent 11 months as City Carrier Assistant for the United States Postal Service. My most recent marketing experience was with Angel Of The Winds Casino Resort. As part of their marketing team, I monitored, and coordinate the social media strategy along with trafficking print and digital advertising. Before that position, I spent two and a half years working with the Everett AquaSox as their Director of Marketing & Digital Media. Some of the duties under this title included marketing all home games externally via social media and our advertising partners. In addition to those duties, I served as an assistant team photographer on game days and managed our media relations. Throughout my time with the Everett AquaSox, I was the graphic designer.

Before relocating to Everett in 2017, I worked at Walmart in Findlay, Ohio, and Albuquerque, New Mexico holding numerous positions including, Customer Service Manager. While in Albuquerque, I worked with Kinesio Holding Corporation as a Graphic Designer in the Creative Team served as the lead for the Felix Hernandez marketing product campaign. I bring multiple years and seasons of experience working in professional and collegiate athletics from the Short-Season Low-A Level of Minor League Baseball to NCAA Division I.

From 2012-14 I served as the Creative Services Manager for the Richmond Flying Squirrels, where I was the marketing manager for all advertisements, web admin, and onsite IT manager. Previously, I served as an intern in the community relations department, where I improved outreach through community appearances and social media.

I graduated with a Masters of Business Administration and a Certificate in Sports Industries from the University of New Haven in 2012 while also serving as a graduate assistant. In addition to my duties as a graduate assistant, I completed an internship with the Central Atlantic Collegiate Conference. Upon completion, I worked for the CACC as their Interim Media Director.

At each organization, I obtained skills beyond those outlined in the job description. I have learned how to be organized, determined, work with diverse experiences and opinions while learning how to set myself apart from the rest.

Thank you in advance for your consideration.

Jason Grohoske

Jason Grohoske

EMAIL: jasongrohoske@gmail.com

PHONE: (419) 889-7963

LINKEDIN: linkedin.com/in/jgrohoske

EDUCATION

MBA, March 2012

University of New Haven, West Haven, CT

Certificate: Sports Industries

BS in Sport Management, December 2009

Defiance College, Defiance, OH

Minor: Graphic Design

WORK EXPERIENCE

PSG Washington Inc., Everett, WA

Account Manager/Marketing Coordinator, May 2021 – December, 2021

United States Postal Service, Everett, WA

City Carrier Assistant, June 2020 – May 2021

Angel Of The Winds Casino Resort, Arlington, WA

Media Coordinator, July 2019 - February 2020

- Managed, monitored and coordinated social media strategy and content
- · Engaged and responded to all Guest reviews, comments and messages on social platforms
- Trafficked and recorded print and digital advertising to advertising partners
- Attended all Team Member and Guest facing events to capture photos and videos for marketing efforts
- Communicated eBlast weekly to new Players Club Members while sending monthly promotions, concert reminders and limited-time offers

Everett AquaSox, Everett, WA

Director of Marketing & Digital Media, February 2018 – June 2019 **Marketing & Website Manager,** January 2017 – February 2018

- Oversaw Everett AquaSox's marketing presence on AquaSox.com, print publications and team's e-newsletter
- Designed all print projects such as pocket schedules, game day program, signage and promotional items
- Engaged with fans through social media channels while promoting games, events and community appearances
- Wrote press releases and supervised Media Relations & Marketing Assistant
- · Assisted with photography during games and served as lead photographer for all outside events
- Sold over \$30,000 in corporate partnerships while surpassing goals in 2018 & 2019
- Generated over \$10,000 in group ticket sales and over \$4,000 in Full Season Equivalents
- Created a relationship with Funko, LLC which led to a multi-year field naming rights agreement
- Co-Race Director for AquaSox 5K managing marketing, corporate partnerships and website
- Functioned as lead contact for AquaSox Pride Nights while building relationships with community partners and LGBTQ organizations

Kinesio Holding Corporation, Albuquerque, NM

Graphic Designer, March 2015 – March 2016

Albuquerque Isotopes, Albuquerque, NM

Graphic Design and Social Media Manager, October 2014 – January 2015

Richmond Flying Squirrels, Richmond, VA

Creative Services Manager, October 2012 – October 2014

Community Relations Intern, April 2012 – October 2012

Jason Grohoske's References

Pat Dillon

Director of Broadcasting Everett AquaSox 425.258.3673 patd@aquasox.com

Tom Denlinger

Vice President Augusta GreenJackets 706.945.4667 tdenlinger@greenjacketsbaseball.com

Phil Bargardi

Vice President of Sales Greenville Drive 864.240.4500 phil.bargardi@greenvilledrive.com

Craig Rutter

Athletic Director Tinora High School 419.497.2621 x1110 crutter@tinora.org

Dan Mara

Commissioner Central Atlantic Collegiate Conference 203.298.4808 dmara@caccathletics.org

Jason Grohoske's Portfolio

https://grohoskephotography.shutterfly.com/